propertyinvesting.net 2011-05-26

# PropertyInvesting.net: Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

PropertyInvesting.net is committed to protecting your privacy. Any questions relating to privacy can be asked by [clicking here](http://www.propertyinvesting.net/content/contact.htm). 

Users are not required to register to use this website. Information is only collected in the following circumstances - if you decide to receive our free PropertyInvesting.net Newsletter. All we require to be collected for this is your name and email address. 

## Information Collection and Use

PropertyInvesting.net collects personally identifiable information when you register for a PropertyInvesting.net Newsletter, free report or submit feedback. PropertyInvesting.net may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.   
When you register as a member of PropertyInvesting.net, we ask for your name, email address, and country of origin. 

PropertyInvesting.net also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP Address, PropertyInvesting.net cookie information, and the page you requested. 

PropertyInvesting.net uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see on our pages, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

**_PropertyInvesting.net will not sell or trade your personally identifiable information to anyone._**

PropertyInvesting.net will only send personally identifiable information about you to third parties when: 

  * We have your consent to share the information; 
  * We need to share your information in order to provide the product or service you have requested; 
  * We need to send the information to companies that work on behalf of PropertyInvesting.net to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us); 
  * We respond to a compulsory court order to comply with due legal process; or 
  * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the PropertyInvesting.net Terms & conditions - or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

**Credit Card Security**

If you place an order for one of our products or services, you will be asked for your name, address and billing information. All orders are processed through Amazon.com or Amazon.co.uk. PropertyInvesting.net will never receive your credit card details. 

See also our Terms & Conditions.

back to top
